* Search bar 
    
    Cancel
    
    #### Trending Searches
    
    #### Top Suggestions

    ### Select Your Language
    
    English

    10
    
    #### Get Your User Profile
    
    FREE | Earn XP | Level Up

[](javascript:void(0))

### Categories

[](javascript:void(0))

Search bar 

Cancel

#### Trending Searches

#### Top Suggestions

10

#### Get Your User Profile

FREE | Earn XP | Level Up

[](javascript:void(0))

### Select Your Language

[](javascript:void(0))

English

The Coolmath Privacy Policy
===========================

Effective Date: May 11, 2024

Coolmath.com LLC (“Coolmath.com”, “Company,” “we,” or “us”) values your privacy. CoolmathGames.com (the “Website”) offers a large collection of games for a general audience.

In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we describe how we collect, use, and share information that we obtain about users on the Website and the services available through these platforms (collectively, “Services”). This Policy does not apply to other Coolmath.com, LLC websites or apps, such as coolmath4kids.com.

CoolmathGames.com is designed for users aged 13 and older. By accessing our Website, you attest that you are at least 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, please visit our kids gaming website at [Coolmath4Kids.com](https://www.coolmath4kids.com/).

By downloading or using the Services, you understand that your information will be handled as described in this Policy. Your use of the Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://www.coolmathgames.com/terms-use), including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes.

**Information We Collect**

We collect information directly from you and your device, from third parties, and by automated means as set out below. The type of information that we collect from you depends on your particular interaction with our Services, but generally includes the information described in the sections below.

_**Information You Provide.**_

You have the option to sign up for an account. When you sign up, you enter a Login ID along with a password. You will also receive an automatically generated username that will be visible to others.

You also have the option to sign up for a subscription to the Services. If you choose to subscribe, you will be required to provide us with your email address, password, and credit card information. You may also create your own username.

We also maintain records of customer service and other communications with users, including the nature of the request, name and contact information. We do not require you to register to use the Website but if you contact us for customer service or support we may maintain your name, contact information and details about your request as a part of our customer relationship management records.

_**Information We Collect Automatically**_

The Services allow users to play interactive games. We automatically collect information about your use of the Services, such as games played, scores, where you left off in the game, the length of time that you use our Services, and other activities on the Website.

We also automatically collect or analyze information about your browser and/or device. This information may include: IP address; device identifiers; device name and model; operating system type, name and version.

We may combine this information with other information that we have collected about you. Please see the section “Analytics and Tracking” below for more information.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use your information for the following purposes:

_**Providing and Improving Our Services.**_ To provide and maintain our Services; to process subscription payments if you’re a Subscriber; to provide troubleshooting; to improve our Services; to develop new features, products, or services; to perform technical operations, such as updating software; and for other customer service and support purposes.

_**Communications.**_ To communicate with you, including via email and push notifications, and to respond to your inquiries.

_**Research and Analytics.**_ To better understand how users access and use our Services, and for other research and analytical purposes, such as to evaluate and improve our services and business operations and to develop additional products, services and features.

_**Protecting Rights and Interests.**_ To protect the safety, rights, property, or security of Coolmath.com, the Services, any third party, or the general public; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to prevent or stop activity that we consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity; to use as evidence in litigation; and to enforce this Policy or our Terms of Use.

_**Legal Compliance.**_ To comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding; to respond to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process; or as part of an investigation or request, whether formal or informal, from law enforcement or a governmental authority.

_**General Business Operations.**_ Where appropriate for the administration of our general business, accounting, recordkeeping and legal functions. As part of our routine business administration, such as employee training, compliance auditing and similar internal activities.

_**Advertising.**_ All or partial advertising on this Website is managed by Playwire LLC. If Playwire publisher advertising services are used, Playwire LLC may collect and use certain aggregated and anonymized data for advertising purposes. To learn more about the types of data collected, how data is used and your choices as a user, please visit [https://www.playwire.com/privacy-policy](https://www.playwire.com/privacy-policy).

**For EU Users only:** If you are located in countries that are part of the European Economic Area, in the United Kingdom or Switzerland, and publisher advertising services are being provided by Playwire LLC, you were presented with messaging from our Consent Management Platform (CMP) around your privacy choices as a user in regards to digital advertising, applicable vendors, cookie usage and more. If you’d like to revisit the choices you have made previously on this Website, please [click here](javascript:window.ramp.showCmpModal();).

We generally process data in the United States. When we share data, we provide data to companies globally. In each case, we have safeguards in place which allow those transfers to happen in a way that ensures data is handled in accordance with the applicable law.

**Disclosure of Information**

In general, we may share your information, including information, as follows:

_**Affiliates.**_ We may share personal information collected with the companies within the Sandbox International Holdings Ltd group of companies. We may disclose the information we collect from you to our affiliates or subsidiaries; however, if we do so, their use and disclosure of your information will be subject to this Policy.

_**Service Providers.**_ We may disclose the information we collect from you to other companies who perform services on our behalf. For example, we may share information with vendors who process subscription payments of our subscribers or who conduct satisfaction surveys on our behalf, in order to improve our site. These service providers are prohibited from retaining, using, or disclosing your information exception as necessary to perform services for us.

_**Advertising Partners.**_ We are an ad-supported business, and we may disclose your information to our advertising partners (such as ad networks and advertisers) where they request the data to select and serve interest-based advertisements and to track the effectiveness of advertisements.

_**Business Transfers.**_ We may disclose your information to another entity in connection with an acquisition or merger, sale or transfer of a business unit or assets, bankruptcy proceeding, or as part of any other similar business transfer, including during negotiations related to such transactions.

_**Protecting Rights and Interests.**_ We may disclose your information to protect the safety, rights, property, or security of Coolmath.com, the Services, any third party, or the general public; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to prevent or stop activity which we, in our sole discretion, may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity; to use as evidence in litigation; and to enforce this Policy or Terms of Use.

_**Legal Compliance.**_ We may disclose your information to comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding; in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process; or as part of an investigation or request, whether formal or informal, from law enforcement or a government official.

_**Aggregate and De-Identified Information.**_ We may share aggregate or de-identified information about users with third parties for research, compliance, or other purposes.

_**Analytics and Tracking**_. We and our third-party service providers use cookies, local storage objects and other tracking mechanisms to track information about your use of our Website. We may combine this information with other information we collect from you (and our third-party service providers may do so on our behalf).

**Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We and our third-party partners use cookies, local storage objects and other tracking mechanisms to track information about your use of our Services, to measure traffic, to collect technical information about visitors’ devices to improve our site, to recognize new or past visitors, to offer interest-based advertisements, to better understand our visitors’ interests, and to observe visitors’ behaviors and browsing activities over time across websites and platforms. We may combine this information with other information we collect from you (and our third-party service providers may do so on our behalf). For more information, visit [About Our Ads](https://www.coolmathgames.com/aboutourads).

We use Google Analytics’ User-ID to collect and analyze information about use of the website and to help us understand activities and trends. As part of this service, we share a unique identifier with Google Analytics. This identifier is not linked to your name or any other individually identifying information we collect about you.

We also use Google Signals to help us better understand your usage of our Services across multiple devices. You can manage the data Google uses for Google Signals by visiting My Activity. You may opt-out of Google Analytics by installing a Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available for download here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**This Site and Children**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our systems. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us personal information, you can email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.coolmathgames.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). 

**Security**

We are committed to maintaining the privacy and integrity of your information no matter where it is stored. We have information security and access policies that limit access to our systems and technology, and we protect data through the use of technological protection measures.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we implement and maintain reasonable measures to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of the information transmitted to us; therefore we do not assume any responsibility for any transmission of your information which you do at your own risk.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Website may contain links to third-party websites or applications. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third-party websites. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third-party websites.

**Questions or Concerns**

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please email us at  
[\[email protected\]](https://www.coolmathgames.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

You can also write to us or call at: Coolmath.com, LLC, Attn: Legal Department, 122 East 42nd Street, Suite 1611, New York, NY 10168, or call us at  
(646) 762 5605

**Policy Changes**

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.

**Addendum for California Residents**

The California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) contains additional terms for California residents using CoolMathGames.com, which are set out in this section.

**Collection and Disclosure of Personal Information**

_Over the past 12 months, we may have collected and disclosed the following categories of personal information from or about consumers or their devices, depending on their use of the Service_:

* Identifiers, such as consumers’ name, address, username, the Google Analytics User ID, and IP address.
    
* Internet or other electronic network activity information, such as cookie information, clickstream information, information about consumers’ participation in surveys, and browsing history pertaining to their use of CoolMathGames.com.
    
* Commercial information about any transactions within CoolMathGames.com (such as payment card information).

We have disclosed consumers’ personal information to the types of entities listed in Disclosure of Information in the body of the Policy.

_We collect your personal information for the following purposes_:

* To operate and improve the Services;
    
* To process surveys;
    
* To serve interest-based advertising;
    
* For security and verification purposes, including to prevent and detect fraudulent activity; and
* To address and remediate technical issues and bugs.

For additional information about how we use consumers’ personal information see How We Use Your Information in the body of the Policy.

[

Hexanaut

Multiplayer Snake Combat](https://www.coolmathgames.com/0-hexanaut-io)

[

##### Custom Profile

Get one for free!](https://www.coolmathgames.com/signup)

##### [Games for Kids](https://www.coolmath4kids.com/)

[

Leaderboards

See how you rank!](https://www.coolmathgames.com/profile/leaderboard)

3. [Coolmath games privacy policy](https://www.coolmathgames.com/privacyp)
    
    If you believe that your own copyrighted content is on our Site without your permission, please follow this [Copyright Infringement Notice procedure](http://coolmath.com/copyright-infringement-notice-procedure).
    
4. COOLMATHGAMES.COM
    -----------------

    BROWSE GAMES
    ------------

    COOLMATH.COM
    ------------

    MORE FROM COOLMATH
    ------------------

    Follow us
    ---------

    English

5. © 2024 Coolmath.com LLC. All Rights Reserved.
